Hello everyone.
My name is Mystic Green Apple.
I'm vocalo, Morimoto Trees.
I am Hiroto Wakai, guitar.
I'm Ryuga Fizer on keyboards.
Now, I'll be watching with you all.
Live Blu-ray DVD Arena Show Utopia is,
It was held at Kanagawa Pier Arena MM on July 8, 2022.
We did it for one night only on the day of our 7th anniversary of our debut.
It is a complete recording of our revival live performance.
It was broadcast live by live viewing and wah-wah,
We had a lot of people watching the live viewing, live streaming by Wah Wah, and peer live streaming.
Thank you very much.
This was the first live concert after we restarted our activities on March 18, 2022,
We were able to have fun with our fans for the first time in a long time.
It was a very memorable day for us to be able to enjoy and meet with our fans.
It has already been more than half a year since then.
More than half a year already?
That's right.
It's too soon.
It's too soon. It's so early.
It's early.
But it's early, but it feels like it was a long time ago.
I know, I know.
Yes, I do.
I know.
There was the tour, too.
That's right.Yes, I have.
Recently.
I would like to share the live video of Utopia with you again.
I would like to talk with you about various topics while we watch it together.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Ready?
Ready? Ready?
Let's start the video. Go ahead!
Here we go.
The tension. It's an exciting time. I'm watching this on video.
I'll get right to it.
We had one rehearsal on this day, right?
That's right.
We had a long time to prepare before the show, but we were only able to do it at the venue.
Yes, we did.
Isn't this the second time we've done this?
Yes, that's right.
Here we are! Utopia!
Cesarean Pool Arena Show Utopia!
It's here!
Because it really means that the first live show in about 2 years is about to begin.
That's right!
We were so nervous, as were the fans.
We were all nervous. The opening video is also wonderful.
It's great! It's wonderful.
What is this?
Beautiful tree! Beautiful tree!Beautiful tree! Beautiful tree!
Isn't it embarrassing? This is how we all do it.
It's a strange feeling
It's a strange feeling.
You made the first prototype of this SE, didn't you, Yo Fujisawa?
That's right.
I'm very excited.
What kind of atmosphere is appropriate for the opening, and how will it be done?
It reminds me a lot of Unity.
The pink, for example, is very appropriate.
With a curtain.
That's right.
I miss it!
Isn't this place so exciting? This music.
This is where it all starts.
What's going to happen?
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
I feel like I did back then.
I want you to look at this.
Look at this... you're all perky.
I'm "par".
I'm a goo.
This is a scissors... we didn't discuss this.
It just so happens to be a go-choki-per.
Each one is different.
I'm a little impressed.I was kind of moved by this, you know, when I saw it.
You're right.
I'm nervous.
I'm very nervous.
The first song is "Attitude".
We've never released a song and played it live before.
That's right.
At Sono in Eden and at the last tour before Kyu Kyu
We never performed it before.
But this is the first time to perform it live, isn't it?
It's difficult to play, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
The moment I played the first note, I thought I had a rough time.
All together.
Tzutzta.
Nice. The groove is changing.
He's in a groove, but he's definitely nervous.
Nervous.
Cool.
That's good.
You're not gonna cry at this?
Yeah, it's like, "Oh my God, I'm gonna cry.
Attitude, as a song on the album, is not a song that I enjoy listening to, because it's very mysterious,
I didn't really imagine how I would feel when I played it live until the show started.
But when the show started and I met all the fans for the first time in two years, I found myself smiling naturally.
I thought of the song as an "attitude" for an album called "Attitude," so I thought of it as a "lead" song,
But I didn't have a chance to perform it in the media, and as I mentioned before, I hadn't performed it live either,However, we didn't have a chance to perform it in the media, and as I mentioned earlier, we didn't perform it live either,
In a sense, it was a song that we were beginning to advance in our music.
But, if we were to come back to the stage after a hiatus, Attitude would probably be the first song we would play,
I was already feeling like I was going to cry a lot. I had been thinking that Attitude would be the first song since the band went on hiatus.
I think you told me about it. You mentioned it early on.
I think it will be difficult to come back to the band until you have the mindset and the skills to play the attitude properly.
I don't think it's going to be easy to come back.
It's an important song, isn't it?
It's difficult to sing here.
Here
Every time, from the rehearsal.
It's so difficult!
How do you sing this?
It's so hard!
The costumes are great, and so are the people!
You guys have amazing hair color!
Yes, they do! Light blue to yellow?
That's amazing!
No, it's nice.
It's like Utopia and Unity are becoming precious,
And it's surrounded by green and pink lights, a fitting staging for the first song.
It was attiude.
Okay, second song.
What was it, the second song?
That one.
Cheers.Cheers.
Cheers, the second song.
I almost said "Ho!
I just want to say it with this call out!
MCs are always interesting, aren't they?
I'm going to say, "I can do it too!
I've already turned it inside out.
Once right there...
Oh, this is my throat today, too!
The famous support bassist.
He had a cute face.
He looked confused.
He was looking for something.
I love the video behind him.
I love it.
That's nice.
This one's from Attitude, too.
Yes, it is.
And Garden of Eden.
The Garden of Eden is over from 2019.
It spanned 2019 to 20 years.
It was our first arena tour.
We played it then as well.
Hasn't this become a standard live song?
Yes, it is.
But usually...
I could say "Cheers".
I see.So.
The Journey
I knew it.
I haven't been able to do any live shows during my absence.
I couldn't do my voice for the first time in my comeback show.
It was the first time I couldn't do it live.
I'm so happy to be here.
I could feel the passage of time
I felt firsthand the passage of time and all the things that had happened.
I really felt it.
But still, the expressions on everyone's faces...
I could see that they were having fun.
I could tell that they were having fun.
I felt it.
I could feel it.
This song made everyone relax, didn't it?
Yeah.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
It's so cool!
But... when we open the Corona, we'll all be together again, right?
I know.
I want to say it.
I want to say it!
I want to say it out loud.
Without any reservations.
I want to say it.
I want to say it out loud!
We've been touring since last November, the ZEPP tour.We've been touring since last November, ZEPP tour, after this tour.
This was the only song in the Reliance sub-prize section that we were allowed to take pictures of.
Cheers!
Yeah, it hurts.
That's good.
What? It's so cool!
It's like a toy, but...
I can call it happy.
You guys look great.
You know, these glow-in-the-dark things on your arms.
Is that a light ring?
It was our first attempt.
It was so cool!
Hey!
Yes! Thank you.
That's great.
Thank you.
I'm so excited.
The third song is that one, right?
That one.
Unexpectedly unexpected.
Wasn't it?
It's an LP.
LP.
This is the debut version, right?
Is it the 3rd mini album?
Like Variety, it's a song called LP.Like Variety, the song is called "LP".
I was in high school when I wrote this.
I think it was around that time.
Even after the passage of time, like this
We were able to play this song in the set without any sense of discomfort.
I was thinking that we were able to play the songs that could be a part of the set without any sense of discomfort.
It's been a while since we did that.
Did you always do this?
Did you always do that?
The Ensemble Tour 2018, I think.
I didn't expect an LP here.
Yes, for sure.
We're pretty good live, you know...
It's a little bit heavier, a little bit bottom-heavy.
Hmmm...
It's more like...
What? Is this where the LP is?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The lyrics are pretty radical, too.
Apparently, we recorded it in March, right around the time we were graduating from high school.
That's right... that's right... that's when we recorded it.
It's too nostalgic!
That's when I was 18, right?
It was around the time I graduated.
What's that?
It's just...
It's not of the variety, but...It's not that variety.
There's a nationally distributed version called Progressive.
Yes, yes, yes.
Even though we haven't graduated yet...
But the staff took the liberty of having a conversation with Omori, who's graduating this spring.
They were like, "You've got to be kidding.
You haven't graduated yet?
Like, "Stop it!
That's right.
That's where the pressure is on.
Desperately.
The last two poems... and then I'd go to bed.
If I go to sleep... you know what I mean?
It's like, "I'm in trouble.
If you don't get an 80 on the last two poems, you won't graduate.
I'm going to take the exam with a passion.
I had to study.
And when I was almost done, I fell asleep.
Why?
I didn't get the last part, but I got over 80.
I'm so happy.
Almost. That's why I wrote everything down.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about Utopia.
I graduated high school.
That's the song I fell in love with.
It's got a kick to it.
The A melody, the intro, the dot-dot-dot...It's called A-melody, intro, dot-dot-dot.
It's impressive, isn't it?
I think the sound of the heart
Dot-dot-dot-dot-dot-dot.
I was making it to remind me of the sound of a heart thumping.
This impression is really fun to play.
Heh...
Surprisingly, me too.
I think I get it.
I don't know...
Oh, yeah, it's a bit like a guitar solo.
Motoki, too.
Surprisingly, it's that twin, isn't it?
That's right.
They're so close together.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, this, here, here, I'm properly feeling and spending time without any evil thoughts, this interlude.
No, because it's so quiet, everyone's voice, of course.
I'm standing here with my eyes closed.
I know, right? That's good.
Why?
Well, I don't know. It's like I'm going solo here.
What are you two thinking about this time?
That's what I'm thinking about.
I'm feeling it. Nothing, of course.
Yeah, I guess.
I'm not strong enough to say I like you the way you are.
I'm not strong enough.Am I not strong enough?
Over and over and over again
Every time I check, it seems like I'm on my way.
Your voice and the video, it's so intense.
And yet it doesn't feel empty.
No, but I like it.
You open up the wound over and over again.
sliverlands
This is where she really starts to sing...
The lyrics.
Oh, I fell
Oh, no.
Me and my high school friends made this together, right?
That's right.
What did you say?
You said it's the third song.
That's right.
We could do it in the middle.
Hey.
So warm.
I love the video.
Oh, wow.
It's a bit...
But, you know, it's been a while.
It's been a while.
It's kind of new.
It's more like...It's not so much about "Oh yeah, yeah, yeah." It's more about...
You can see this live from a slightly different perspective.
from a different perspective.
What's going to happen next?
It's so fresh!
They're going to upload the video.
I'm getting a little emotional.
It's so fresh!
That's great. That's really great.
That's terrible.
It was like we finally met, you know?
Yes, it was.
First live performance in two and a half years.
We're all hoping for the same thing, right?
That's a lot of applause, isn't it?
Yes, today was our first show in two and a half years.
But it seems he can't speak.
Oh, well...
That's why.
Oh, hey.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, no.
We're saying the same thing.
Oh, my God.
MC with MC.
That's a great color.That's a hell of a color.
I don't know what kind of applause that is.
What kind of applause is that?
Good applause, good applause, good applause.
I know it's hard, but...
It's the first time I've ever heard you do that.
That's right, that's right.
If you stop or something, you can't speak anymore.
But...
You just included facial expressions, didn't you? Not just clapping.
You were animated just now.
I would like to have it today, OK?
Not only at this venue today.
It's not only at this venue today, but also through live viewing.
I understand that there are people who are enjoying the live streaming and live broadcast.
Can you see me?
Well, I mean, I can see you through this.
I mean, you can reach people on YouTube.
I'm a traffic engineer.
I can see you.
Hey...
I see you, too.
We see you, too.
I'm scared.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What's up with that?
How do you feel about that, Ryou?How do you feel about that, Ryo-chan?
Oh, no.
It's been a while.
It's been a while since I've seen you.
It's been a while since I've written to you, but not many people write to me on Sue.
A little.
You're basically the same.
You've been chewing a lot.
Ryo-chan!
Ryo-chan.
Thank you.
You're right.
You're sad about yourself.
That's great. No, that's a good point.
That's a good one.
That's a nice thing to say, this early in the game.
That's a good point.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm not celebrating.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
It makes me nervous.
Hey, guys.
I'm trying not to laugh behind my mask.
They're celebrating.Celebratory tinkering.
I'm young.
I have a grass crown.
I'm often mistaken for a celebrant.
I think it's a crown.
A grass crown.
I wanted to meet everyone.
You know...
We really missed you, too.
What's that?
Her eyes...
You cried, didn't you?
Yes, I was crying.
I was crying.
But today is a really special day.
I hope we can create the best utopia together.
I hope we can all make the best of this utopia together.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Good MC.
I'm going to say it with gusto, are you ready?
Are you ready?
Um, well, you have a seat, but you can move your body.
That's right.
Just enjoy yourself, okay?
Yeah.
Okay, just like that.Well, then, that's how it is.
I'll be looking forward to working with you today.
Let's go.